I'm out at the bottom of the hall, and I'm looking for all of you.
I'd like to collect some congratulations on 50 years.
The Hawaii Pad people are so cute!
Hawa and Hina-chan.
They're so cute.
So cute.
Amazing.
I'm so happy
Glad to hear it.
Good evening everyone. Why are you filming YouTube? I'll tell you why I'm here.
Do you want to say the title once?
I'll do my best.
Happy 465th Anniversary of Hyuga Junior High School! A big barrage of surprises!
Yay!
Surprisingly, it fits.
Ta-da!
What is it?
I thought it was a reflector.
Correct.
It's just right.
It is not a reflector,
It's big. It's amazing.
One meter by one meter.
1m1m. 1m1m.
1m1m1m.
It's a piece of cloth.
This is the big banner,
I would like to have a message from all the people of the sun who came to the 5th Hinatan Festival here.
I would like to receive them.
I would like to have a message from the people of the sun who came to the 5th Hinatan Festival.
We would like to sneak into the festival.
I wonder if they will notice us?
What? I don't think they will. I don't think so.
But on the other hand, it would be a little sad if they don't find out.
I understand. That's how I feel,
I want to go to be found out, don't you?
I'd like to go to the bye. I'd like to go bye-bye for a bit.
Fast forward
Fast forward.
If we don't get caught, we've successfully infiltrated.
That's what it means.
At the end of the day, they don't know about it yet.
Is that right?
That's right.
So I hope to surprise everyone with a big surprise at the end.
We will do our best as a staff so that everyone will praise us with lots of congratulations.
We, as staff members, will do our best.
We'll do our best.
Now, let's go undercover!
It's the first day of the Hinasan Festival!
Now, as I told you yesterday, you're going to cheer on the staff.
Go outside the venue.
I'm going to go with your husband.
I'd like to collect words of congratulations for 50 years
I'm nervous
You're pretty tired.
I'm looking forward to it
Good luck
I'll have them do their best
I'll do my best not to fall apart.
I'll be there.
I'm looking forward to it.
Outside of gigs, outside of events...
There's no such thing as a sub, right?
I'm so happy
This is a special case.
Special case.
How did it go?
Are you comfortable with it?
I'm comfortable with it.
I really don't have any roses.
I'm sure it's gonna be a blast. mess around
Not a rose, not a rose, not a rose, not a rose, not a rose
Not at all.
Nothing at all.
I can't even get a temp.
It's really not roses.
Yes, sir.
Yes. Yes.
Yes. - Yes.
Yes, sir.
Yes Yes
Thank you for watching
ah ah ah ah ah ah
ár
in imaginary spit
I think it's pretty good.
me
I don't know...
I don't know.
I'm sure she'd love to see it.
Who is the housewife?
Shiro Sato
Can I write something like that for him?
Then, put it on Sato.
Write something like this. Can I write something like this at all?
Can I do it?
For the girl who's there.
Who's there?
Oh!
Ooh.
Thank you
Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am.
You're the queen.
Spring
Oh, it's happening.
Spring hitter
It's going so well.
Sing already?
What song?
What should we sing?
You want to make it a regular song?
Ask her again today.
Okay. - Okay.
Just humming.
I'll try.
Do you think they'll know?
You'll know.
You can't sing all the time.
When you were writing this.
I didn't want it to be too subtle.
I wanted to leave the middle open.
Like right here. Like around here.
You're on your third one now, top.
Please.
You have a visitor today?
Yes, sir.
What song are you going to play?
Well, I like Mibu, so I'll choose one.
What do you like about Mibu-chan?
Yes, I do.
The duo who runs the store.
Do you like to store together?
I like all of them.
Well, tell her when you're done.
No problem.
Thank you very much.
I'll take your recommendation.
Wanchise.
This one is prettier.
It's a girl.
A girl.
Hanasaki-san?
Please
Please.
Yes, ma'am.
May I ask you something?
Who is your favorite?
I graduated yesterday, but I didn't go again.
No, I didn't go yesterday.
Today, I'm doing Wayward and Ayaka-like.
I wish you could come.
But Ayaka is graduating too.
I'm so sad.
By the way, I'm going to be in the 3rd or 4th term from the new 2nd term.
It's so cute that they really want to find a new box!
Recently, Hina KawadaLately, it's been Hina Kawada.
Heh.
Cute, isn't she?
Cute water.
She's cute, isn't she?
I'm glad.
Here you go. First.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
You're very important, Mr. Kurt.
Mr. Kurt.
My pleasure.
Thank you, brother.
I'm glad
Congratulations
Congratulations!
I got to meet Kurt's fans.
At the end, Mr. Kurt even prompted me.
He was a kind fan.
Thank you very much.
We made it.
Isn't that great?
We talked a lot, didn't we?
I did a lot of talking.
I'm surprised it took you this long to get used to it.
Yes, it was.
But I'm glad we had such a good time going undercover.
Let's try our best to have fun!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
Two days of Hinata Festival is over!
Good morning.
Haruharu and I went to hide under the sun the other day to collect comments.
The staff has been working with me and it looks like they've already finished it.
I haven't seen a single one yet.
I haven't seen anything yet.
Wow! There are more than I thought there would be! Wow!!! There's more than I thought there would be!
Ta-da!
I'm so happy!
From hiragana break to Hinata's
Thank you for all the excitement and memories of Hinataka 46 so far!
I wrote that I have no choice but to promote Hinata and 46
I'm so happy!
I'll read it all later.
I'll read them all later.
Hinata Taro...
I don't understand.
A little more like this...
I don't know...
It is completed.
I am very happy to have received your messages today, and I am looking forward to showing them to everyone,
I'm looking forward to showing it to everyone from now on,
I am also looking forward to showing them to everyone, and I could also feel the love of the people of the sun other than those who wrote here today and yesterday at the Hinatan Festival,
We also felt the love of the people of the sun other than what you wrote here today and yesterday at the Hinatan Festival, so we would like to do our best to return the favor to the sun.
I want to send lots of love to everyone.
I can't wait to show it to everyone!
It was truly a wonderful live performance.
Cheers to you all for your awards this morning as well!
Excuse me, can I start right away?
I know this is a difficult one for all of you.
Stan please give them to you and give your comments.
Wow!
That's great!
And two of us to collect.
Stay in and out!
Yeah!
So much thought has gone into this ladle,
I hope you will all read the whole thing without shimmying.
The finished big ladle!
Here it is.
Come in for a moment.
Yes, yes, yes. Yes, yes, yes.
Go.
I recommend it.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Yay.
Me too.
It's a bit of a distance thing.
I call you Hime-chan.
Hime-chan.
Look at me.
Please look.
I saw too much, so I came.
Too much?
Seriously, can I call you?
I'll call him.
Wait, there's a girl who knows.
Oh, my gosh.
It's for Hime-chan.
No, it's not.
Thanks, I got it.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Thank you. Here it is.
It's cute.
It makes me happy.
I'm so happy.
I'm really happy.
To all of you.
You don't talk.
They know.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's going to be infectious.
It's Mosaic now.
With Mosaic now.
Mosaic. In Mosaic.
In Mosaic.
Mosaic.
It's no good. If I show it, it's like this.
Is that so?
That's right.
At the bottom.
It's no good, if I show you this.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, there they are.
Hey.
That's amazing.
Ah, he's cute.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Treasure.
Yes, I love Aya and Meimei.
I love Aya and Meimei.
I love you too, Mina-chan.
I'm so happy.
Wow.
I'll go next time.
Stace.
Wow.
Oh.
Amazing.
My smile was so big, even my hands were aligned.
It's me.
It's me. Soothe.
I'm happy.
It's sweet to hear a live voice.
It's delicious.
It's amazing.
It's really great.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Congratulations on your 5th anniversary.
Nipan's smile cheers me up every day.
I sincerely wish Hinatazaka46's success from now on.
I'm glad you love Nipan. Love.
He writes the translation of his success in Hirabana.
We are similar, aren't we?
My translation is similar too.
I'm glad.
Oh, Naochan is here.
Naochan?
Is it purple?
Oh, I found it.
It's true, it's written.
It's true.
Yes, I read it too.
I read it.
I'm so glad.
Thank you very much.
Oh, I found it.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
Can you tell who my fans are or what? Do you know who my fans are?
Karuya-chan, Nano-chan...
Meimei, Nano-chan...
Wow! I want to find a gold bra!
Ah!
Thank you!
I found it!
You gave me love, so I'll give you love back.
Excuse me.
I'll tell him I saw it too.
Oh, come in! With me! With me!
No! Come with us.
Oh, my God!
I'll miss you.
I'm so happy.
Thank you so much.
A lot of stations
Thank you so much
Thank you for all your customers
Thank you for your support for the fifth year.
Sixth year?
Fifth anniversary, sixth year.
Wow! I'm so happy!
Ah! Hime-chan's smile always cheers me up!
Please keep up the good work!
I'm so happy! Thank you! I'll do my best with a smile after that!
Cute!
Cute! Keep smiling!
I'm getting it! I'm more passionate about this one!
You're in service!
Thank you! I'm impressed!
Thank you very much!
Thanks to you, I bought a toy!
Thanks to you, I bought a toy.
Thank you so much.
I did it all at once.I did it all at once.
I am so happy.
I'm very happy.
So we will continue to do our best.
Please continue to come and help everyone.
Thank you very much.
Wow, wow, wow.
What!
It says Riki-chan and me.
I love Riki-chan and Rio-chan.
I'm so happy.
I'm so surprised.
I'm a little bit sad.
How's it going?
It's great.
Oh, wow!
Thank you.
Please take a look.
Hirahon, I always support you.
Thank you very much.
I've been to the same place.
Eh! I see.
It's a girl.
A real ninnishi.
Hey.
Thanks for all the happiness.
Thank you.
Please look forward to it. Four geographical bureaus.
Please look forward to it.
Thank you very much.
It's really warm, isn't it?
Hey.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
You have written.
Thank you very much.
I read a lot.
I am glad.
Thank you very much.